baymard.com 2011-12-03

# Privacy Policy - Baymard Institute

This Privacy Policy explains how we handle your personal data and it applies to the products and services of Baymard Institute, such as [www.baymard.com](http://www.baymard.com/) and any pages or subdomains hereof.

_Last updated: 1 March, 2011_

## Unsubscribing

If you subscribe to our Newsletter you can unsubscribe by using the “unsubscribe link” placed in the bottom of every email or send an email to [info@baymard.com](mailto:info@baymard.com) with the subject “unsubscribe”.

## Collected information

We store e-mail addresses and e-mails from those who contact us by e-mail or web forms.

We collect anonymous data on what web pages and data are accessed on our website.  
We store information submitted voluntarily by filling in web forms, surveys, site registrations and similar.

## Usage of information

We use the data to: offer our products and services, authentication and validation, product improvements, research, contact and billing.

## Information sharing

We will never give, sell or rent your personal data to anyone, unless stated otherwise in this privacy policy, or in special cases such as subpoenas, investigations and prevention of illegal behavior, or unless you request so.

If Baymard Institute is acquired or merged with another company we will notify you to the extent possible before your information is transferred and then become subject to their privacy policies.

## Data storage

Baymard Institute use 3rd party hosting providers and processing partners for providing the technology required to run our products and services.

## Security

Credit Card data is handled and stored securely using 128-bit SSL encryption, in complete compliance with VISA and MasterCard approved PCI standards for secure online payments.

## Cookies and links

When you visit our website or use our services we store a “cookie” on your computer – a small data file that contains a string of characters – that are used for identifying you, your preferences, service access and so on.

From our sites we might link to external sites that are not affiliated or owned by Baymard Institute, this Privacy Policy only applies to the products and services of Baymard Institute. You should look into the privacy policy of the external sites if you want to know what applies for them.

## Policy updates

This Privacy Policy might change from time to time. Such changes will appear on this Privacy Policy page.

## Questions

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy they can be addressed to [privacy@baymard.com](mailto:privacy@baymard.com) or to this address: Baymard Institute, Aksel Moellers Have 18 5tv, 2000 Copenhagen, Denmark.
